[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to historians this indigo-colored vegetable originates from India.  However, there are some written accounts from the 5th century in China, which indicate its cultivation there as well.", "correct_answer": "Eggplant", "incorrect_answers": ["Celery", "Pumpkin", "Cucumber"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what US city is the Lincoln Memorial located?", "correct_answer": "Washington, DC", "incorrect_answers": ["Wilmington, DE", "New York, NY", "Louisville, Kentucky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dish of fresh squid is eaten alive and raw, even at the moment of swallowing it.", "correct_answer": "Ika sashimi", "incorrect_answers": ["Hachi no ko", "Inago", "Mollejas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Uncontrolled hypertension (high blood pressure) leads to all of the following EXCEPT this one.", "correct_answer": "Thyroid disease", "incorrect_answers": ["Heart disease", "Kidney failure", "Stroke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed Count Dracula in the 1992 horror movie Dracula?", "correct_answer": "Gary Oldman", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard E. Grant", "Keanu Reeves", "Anthony Hopkins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Superman Returns, Lois and Jason visit Superman at the hospital while he is in a coma.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these popular cocktails is a variation of the pineapple cocktail Pina Colada?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Chi Chi", "Lava Flow", "Miami Vice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cars were stolen by thieves who wrote down VINs (car serial numbers)  and used them to obtain duplicate keys through auto dealerships.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a chow in the game of Mahjong?", "correct_answer": "a meld of three suited tiles in sequence", "incorrect_answers": ["a meld of four suited tiles in sequence", "a meld of two suited tiles in sequence", "a meld of six suited tiles in sequence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A reddish ring around the moon means this.", "correct_answer": "Rain or snow", "incorrect_answers": ["Rainbow or bright sunshine", "Fog or haze", "Wind or rain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie was honored with the Oscar for Best Picture at the 57th Academy Awards in 1985?", "correct_answer": "Amadeus", "incorrect_answers": ["A Passage to India", "Places in the Heart", "The Killing Fields"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Animal House, before giving Larry and Kent their Delta names, Bluto gives names to two other pledges. What is the name of the guy just before Larry?", "correct_answer": "Mothball", "incorrect_answers": ["Weiner", "Stork", "Jaybird"]}]